{
    "id": "838e04a9eb2f46d88c3b16f273c1a32b",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Don’t you ……………… listen to what I say?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… matters.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Nothing",
                "Not anything"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I opened the door, but I …………… see nobody.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "could",
                "couldn't"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither of my brothers …………….. here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Ruth didn’t turn up, and James didn’t ………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She was only talking like that because she ………………. nervous.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have only ………………. to India once.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "been",
                "gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… given a medal for living with her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ought be",
                "ought to be"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ran ……………….. the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "out of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He has got no ideas of ……………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "his",
                "his own"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}